(uneasy music)
(bell chiming in distance)
(hand knocking)
(uneasy music continues)
- You gonna stand there all
night or you gonna let me in?
- Come in.
Stop.
Turn around.
(uneasy music continues)
Alright, come on.
Come on.
(uneasy music continues)
(Guy snorting)
(people speaking foreign
language)
- Clean.
Clean and beautiful.
I never imagined that the
lotus be more beautiful
than the real flower.
I'm Guy.
- Are we gonna do this or what?
(people speaking foreign
language)
You wouldn't want a little
foreplay
before the transaction?
- I've got places to be.
(Guy speaking foreign language)
- There's the goods.
Where's the money?
(people speaking foreign
language)
(tense music)
(Guy continues speaking foreign
language)
(dramatic music)
(punches thudding)
(Guy speaking foreign language)
(dramatic music continues)
(people fighting)
(tense music)
(thug laughing)
(dramatic music)
(people fighting)
(dramatic music continues)
(dramatic music)
(people fighting)
(slow suspenseful music)
- Come on, go.
(dramatic music)
(people fighting)
(man yelling)
(dramatic music continues)
(man groaning)
- [Mr. White] Spinning our
wheels here
with some of these recruits,
they're good though,
but they, they lack experience.
- She has field experience,
is dedicated and has been
working intel on LaFleur
for four years.
- [Mr. White] She speaks French
as well.
- [Cindy] Native tongue.
- [Mr. White] You think
she has what it takes?
I heard she had to take some
time off.
(dramatic music)
- She's past that now.
- Okay.
- Come with me, Agent Chen.
You can relax, the mission was a
success.
(uneasy music)
Thanks to your intel,
we now have Nikolai in custody
and know the location
of Marcel's next deal.
- That's excellent news.
- The man who just left here is
Mr. White.
He runs a specialised unit.
I believe you applied some years
ago.
- Yes ma'am, that's right.
- A sting operation on Marcel is
to take place tomorrow at
sunrise.
He believes you should take the
lead.
- Me, ma'am?
- Who better else to bring this
home?
- I dunno what to say.
- You say yes.
This is your chance.
I get it.
Work life balance isn't easy.
What we do here, Lily, is hard
and it requires sacrifice.
(soft music)
- Hey babe, all set.
I cannot wait
to get some peace and quiet
away from the city's chaos.
- Yeah, it's gonna be great.
- Everything okay?
You seem a bit off.
- Oh no, it's nothing,
- Huh?
- Wow.
- Got a new one.
(Lily laughing)
A Buddhist walks into a bar
and he says, can you make
me one with everything?
- Okay, okay.
- Because he's a Buddhist.
You like music?
- No.
- CDs?
(light music continues)
- Did you move my ladder?
Because you need it.
- Why?
- To get on my level.
(light music continues)
So my boss reached out with the
idea
of me starting to work remotely.
What do you think?
Could get outta the city.
Reduce our expenses.
Besides if we did that we can
even make do on one salary.
Okay, Lil spill it.
Something is off.
It's not you taking a step back.
- I know, but they want me
to take the lead on this.
You know how important that is
to me.
- Was.
- I've been tracking LaFleur for
years.
- You've been gathering intel,
Lily.
And you've done an incredible
job.
But why not let someone
else take it from here?
You in the field.
Hey.
We've been down this road
before.
- This is different.
- How?
- If things go well,
maybe I finally get my shot.
- Let me tell you how this plays
out.
You with the insane hours, the
late nights
and me here waiting.
I don't wanna wait anymore.
- This is about more than just
me or us.
It's about creating a safer
place for our future family.
(soft music)
- I need to take a walk.
Don't wait up.
- John.
John.
(soft music continues)
- Ta-da.
It's tradition.
I get one at the start of the
journey.
You get one at the end.
(soft music continues)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [John] Who?
Who are you?
- John, is that you?
- [The Voice] What's your name?
- What?
- You're name!
- [John] John.
John Richardson.
- John!
- [The Voice] And what am
I holding in my hand, John?
- [John] I, I don't know.
What am I?
- [The Voice] What am I holding?
- [John] You're holding
a hammer.
- [The Voice] Agent Chen,
do I have your attention?
- [Lily] Who is this?
- [The Voice] If you want
to see your husband alive,
follow my instructions.
You have 10 minutes to reach
the address I'm sending you.
If you do anything but
what I ask, John dies.
(tense music)
- John.
(engine revving)
(tense music continues)
(horn honking)
(phone ringing)
- [The Voice] Congratulations,
Lily.
You made it here in record
breaking time.
- What do you want from me?
- [The Voice] In the backseat,
you'll find two bags.
Open the one on the left.
(suspenseful music)
A meet is about to take
place between a contact
who goes by the alias
Lotus and a man named Guy.
- Guy, as in LaFleur's enforcer?
- [The Voice] Precisely.
You are to play a role.
Lotus is a contact that Guy has
never met.
Your task is to gain his trust
and when the moment is
right, eliminate him.
- No, no.
Forget it, I'm not doing that.
- [The Voice] I think you will
if you value John's life.
Go to the furniture store.
Knock four times.
(suspenseful music)
(LaFleur speaking French)
(people fighting)
(Guy speaking French)
(Guy coughing)
(both speaking French)
(tense music)
(classical music)
- Mr. Chairman.
(LaFleur speaking French)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
(classical music continues)
- Marcel, you wanted to see me?
- I did.
(classical music continues)
Well, aren't you gonna say
anything?
How about my house?
- Oh, very nice.
- [LaFleur] Not impressed.
Follow me.
- Actually, I think I--
After you.
(artist singing in French)
- [LaFleur] Not many
people get to see this.
(artist continues singing in
French)
- You paint?
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- We call it a hug.
This is my latest creation.
(suspenseful music)
A reflection of the
city, wouldn't you agree?
- Oh yeah, sure.
(uneasy music)
- But then again,
one can only paint with
the colours they're given.
And you, my friend,
have not been giving me the
right colours.
- Marcel, I have no--
(flesh slicing)
(classical music playing)
(blood spattering)
- Ah.
(classical music)
(tense music)
(phone ringing)
- Yes?
- [The Voice] Lily, I gotta
admit, you impressed me tonight.
I knew you had it in you to
kill.
- No, that that was
self-defense.
- [The Voice] Really?
I'm sure Director Bass would
second that.
- Why are you doing this?
- [The Voice] I have my mission
and you are most suited for it.
- I did what you asked, now let
John go.
- [The Voice] You've made a
start, but we're not done yet.
Two more targets remain.
You will finish them by dawn.
- I won't do it.
- [The Voice] Let's ask
John about that, shall we?
(tense music)
John?
What am I holding right now?
- [John] It's a hacksaw.
- [The Voice] And how does
it look, this hacksaw?
- [John] It's rusty.
And it's dull.
- Wait, no, stop please.
(tense music)
- [The Voice] How does that
feel?
- Okay, wait, okay, I'll do it.
Just please stop hurting him.
- [The Voice] There's a good
girl.
I'll send you another address.
Now take a breath, you
have a long night ahead.
- Any leads on Guy's, death?
- Not as of yet.
We've taken a handful of
his thugs into custody.
- Well, what's the current
story?
- Looks like a drug deal went
sideways.
Found Guy dead, scissors
lodged in his neck
right next to a mattress
brimming with cocaine.
- Could this be linked to the
upcoming deal with Marcel?
- That's still uncertain.
- Okay.
Get agent Chen in here.
- I don't believe Chen's in,
ma'am.
(quiet music)
(engine revving)
(phone ringing)
- Hello?
- [Director Bass] Agent
Chen, are you on your way in?
- I'm not coming in, ma'am.
- [Director Bass] What do you
mean you're not coming in?
- Something came up.
It's personal.
- [Director Bass] We just found
Marcel's main muscle dead.
I need you here now.
- I am sorry,
but I just can't.
- [Director Bass] You
realise you're putting
your entire career on the line?
- I understand.
(soft music)
(phone ringing)
- [The Voice] You've
been a bad girl, Lily.
You spoke to your boss.
I told you not to alert the
authorities.
- I had to get her off my case.
Otherwise, the entire agency
would be looking for me.
- [The Voice] Fine, I believe
you for now.
But keep in mind, disobedience
will cost
John more than a finger next
time.
- I wanna talk to John.
- [The Voice] No, no, not
until you finish the next task.
Take the other bag from the
backseat.
- Okay, I have it.
- [The Voice] Open it.
Now get dressed.
Your next target is Jimmy Chen.
Are you familiar with him?
- Yes.
He's the head of LaFleur's
money laundering operations.
- [The Voice] Correct.
Jimmy frequents a club named
Zen.
Infiltrate the club, drop
the pill into his drink
and exit through the back door.
- That's suicide.
Every Triad in the city
hangs out in there.
- [The Voice] I have faith in
you.
Put in the earpiece
and I'll guide you through it.
- How am I supposed to find him?
No one even knows what he looks
like.
- [The Voice] In the bag,
you'll find a necklace
with a hidden camera.
Put it on.
I'll be your eyes in the club.
As long as you do your part,
John will be just fine.
(electronic music)
(artist singing in French)
Remember, if you wanna survive
blend in.
(electronic music continues)
(artist singing in French)
You might find it useful to
order a drink
and pretend to relax.
(electronic music continues)
(artist singing in French)
- Vodka martini please.
- [The Voice] I doubt the people
here use the word "please".
- Shaken or stirred?
- Just give me the fucking
drink.
- [The Voice] That's more like
it.
(electronic music continues)
(artist singing in French)
What's wrong?
- That's Chau Wong.
I arrested him five years ago.
- [The Voice] Then
we'll have to move fast.
Start walking around the club.
I'll tell you where to find
Jimmy.
(dance music)
- So what's your end game in all
this?
Remove some rivals?
Maybe take over the LaFleur's
throne?
- [The Voice] Amusing, but no,
my intentions are far more
interesting.
- Spoken like a true mastermind.
- [The Voice] Careful Agent
Chen.
You of all people should know
the dangers
of a kidnapping.
(dance music continues)
Eyes right.
You may find an individual of
interest.
(dance music continues)
- That's Jimmy?
- [The Voice] Don't be fooled
by his boyish good looks.
Now find a way to get close.
(dance music continues)
- Sorry.
So sorry.
(dance music continues)
(Jimmy speaking foreign
language)
(dance music continues)
- Quite a cosy setup you got
here, Jimmy.
- LaFleur,
you shouldn't be here.
(dance music continues)
- [The Voice] What's happening?
- It's LaFleur.
He's here.
- [The Voice] You're sure it's
him?
- We have a problem.
A mutual friend, Guy met
an untimely end tonight.
- I had nothing to do with that.
- I'm sure.
- Didn't say you did.
- [The Voice] Get closer.
- But it seems I got a
leak and I need to plug it.
- Plug it how?
- There's two types of people
that could have done this,
both work for me.
The ones on the streets
or the ones in power.
- [Jimmy] What's your point?
- My money isn't safe and
I want it moved tonight.
- You know I can't do that.
- You know what will happen if
you don't?
- You're threatening me?
(LaFleur speaking French)
(thug laughing)
(Jimmy speaking foreign
language)
- Watch it, LaFleur.
You're in my territory now.
- [The Voice] You've been made.
You're out of time.
Kill him now!
- I knew it was you.
(dramatic music)
(LaFleur speaking foreign
language)
(dramatic electronic music)
♪ Let's do it ♪
(dramatic electronic music
continues)
(people screaming)
(dramatic music continues)
(punches thudding)
(Jimmy speaking in foreign
language)
(dramatic music continues)
(people fighting)
(dramatic electronic music
continues)
(Jimmy speaking foreign
language)
(dramatic music)
- [Jimmy] Fuck.
(suspenseful music)
- Who are the people in
power working for LaFleur?
- [The Voice] End it now, Lily.
(Jimmy mumbles)
- Kill my whole family.
- [The Voice] Kill him.
Kill him!
- Tell me or else.
- [John] Please, no.
Not again.
(Lily groans)
(dramatic music)
(Jimmy screaming)
(glass breaking)
(metal crunching)
(horn honking)
(tense music)
- [The Voice] Lily.
Lily.
Get to your car.
(horn continues honking)
- [Lily] Just gimme the next
target.
- [The Voice] Your next
target is Nikolai Petrov.
- [Director Bass] The
mission was a success.
We now have Nikolai in custody.
- [The Voice] A trusted member
of Marcel's inner circle.
Nikolai has with him
information vital to Marcel.
- [Director Bass] Thanks to your
intel,
the location of Marcel's next
deal.
- [The Voice] He's
retreated to a safe house
outside Marcel's reach.
- We already extracted that
information.
- [The Voice] Oh, I'm
not talking about that.
- Then what?
- [The Voice] Let's just say
there's part of the puzzle
you're better off not knowing.
Your mission now is to retrieve
the intel held by Nikolai
and then take him out before
Marcel does.
- I'm gonna need a weapon this
time.
- [The Voice] You'll find
what you need in the trunk.
- [Lily] Send me the address.
- [The Voice] Well, I'm afraid
I don't have that information.
Isn't gathering intel your
forte?
(artist singing in foreign
language)
- There are rumours
they are going after my
organisation.
(LaFleur speaking French)
Stick to the plan.
If I'm right, which I usually
am,
I know exactly where they'll go
next.
(engine revving)
(soft music)
- Try this.
No?
(Lily laughing)
(tense music)
(computer beeping)
- I need you here.
(suspenseful music)
Lily?
What's going on?
- I need to talk to you, ma'am.
(artist singing in foreign
language)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- [LaFleur] Who is she?
(man screaming)
- Just a government agent.
Lily Chen.
Fuck.
Pull it out!
(man screaming)
(artist singing in foreign
language)
- Your turn, love.
(artist continues singing
in foreign language)
(bones cracking)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- What do we do about that
agent?
- Did you find Nikolai?
- Oui.
- Then leave the rest to me.
- Looking a little bruised.
Everything okay?
- I don't want to get into that.
- Does this have something to do
with
John?
- No.
I'm here to resign.
- You've just got the
position you've always wanted
and you're resigning?
You should sleep on this.
- I have.
I've made up my mind.
- Where's this coming from?
- That's none of your business.
- With all due respect, Lily,
what the fuck's gotten into you?
(phone ringing)
- I need to take this.
- Now?
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(Lily speaking French)
- [Lily] I have to go.
- [Director Bass] Lily!
(engine revving)
(phone ringing)
- [The Voice] That was risky
what you did.
I hope you didn't do anything
rash,
for John's sake.
- You told me to figure it
out, so that's what I did.
- [The Voice] Fair enough.
I trust you realise LaFleur's
mobilised against you.
Don't underestimate him.
(engine revving)
(elevator bell dinging)
- Status?
- All clear.
- Check it again.
- Copy that.
(uneasy music)
- Shit.
(uneasy music continues)
(cars approaching)
(uneasy music)
(suspenseful music)
(Nikolai humming)
- [Agent] Hey,
knock it off.
(punches thudding)
(people groaning)
- Hey, hey, hey, don't shoot.
Who are you?
Hello?
(tense music)
- She is here.
- Marcel wants her alive.
(tense music)
- We need to get you outta here.
- I don't understand.
- You will when Marcel's people
put a bullet in your head.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
(tense music)
Shit.
(elevator dings)
(tense music continues)
(radio chatter)
(people shouting in distance)
(tense music continues)
- [Agent] Over here.
Move it.
Move it, move it.
(tense music continues)
(person groaning)
(gun shots firing)
(tense music continues)
(flesh ripping)
(man groaning)
(tense music continues)
(knife slicing)
(man groaning)
- Come on.
(suspenseful music)
(gun shots firing)
(people groaning)
Come on.
(suspenseful music continues)
(gun shots firing)
Go.
(suspenseful music continues)
(gun shots firing)
- You're tapped.
- Shut up.
(suspenseful music continues)
- Ha ha, no, no, no, no.
(gun shots firing)
- Shit.
- Marcel
wants you alive.
How about we settle this
the old fashioned way?
- How about I put two in your
chest?
- It might be hard with no
bullets.
We'll make it fair.
(suspenseful music continues)
- Make me come.
- Your girlfriend isn't joining
us?
(suspenseful music continues)
- She likes to watch.
(tense music)
(both fighting)
(tense music continues)
- Oh yeah.
(both fighting)
(tense music continues)
Romeo!
(Romeo screaming)
(suspenseful music)
(tense music)
(all fighting)
(tense music continues)
(suspenseful music)
- Harder.
- Harder?
- Make it harder.
(suspenseful music continues)
- I can make it harder.
I'll make it harder.
- Oh yeah.
Oh yeah.
(tense music continues)
(Juliette moaning)
(suspenseful music)
- Harder.
Come on, give it to me.
(tense music)
Oh yeah.
(tense music continues)
(Juliette moaning)
(suspenseful music)
(gun shot fires)
(uneasy music)
- Okay.
I know who you are,
who you work for.
- Give me the intel on Marcel.
- What intel?
(gun shot fires)
- Wait.
You have no idea what they're
capable of.
- Little late to be worrying
about that.
(gun shot fires)
(Nikolai screaming)
- Fine.
I'll tell you.
Marcel, he's linked to your
agency.
- I already know that.
Why are you hiding?
What do you have on him?
- I'm not hiding, you idiot.
Huh, don't you get it?
Marcel wanted me here.
He wanted me to tell you
and I did, spoon fed you.
- What are you saying?
- It was a diversion
for him and your people
to do the real exchange.
Yeah.
- [Lily] Where?
- Oh, that's above my pay grade.
- You better ask for a raise.
- Oh, okay.
Is private compound
just north of the city.
Greater Road.
That's all I know.
- Well, Nikolai,
I guess you're no longer of use
to me.
- No, no, no, no.
(suspenseful music)
Please.
(suspenseful music continues)
(phone ringing)
(suspenseful music)
- [The Voice] Is it done?
- It is.
- [The Voice] You disappoint me,
Lily,
and your husband will pay for it
- If you hurt him, I'll kill
you.
- Like you did Nikolai?
- I'm warning you.
- [The Voice] Hey Lily.
(John screaming)
- John?
- And next time--
- John!
- [The Voice] Oh, you can
scream better than that.
Come on, Lily.
- Stop.
(John groaning)
Stop.
- [The Voice] Come on,
Lily, you can do this.
- Stop.
- John's banging you to.
How that feel John?
(suspenseful music)
Come here, you little fuck.
- I'm sorry.
- [The Voice] Come on, Lily.
He's calling for you.
(suspenseful music)
(gun shot fires)
Lily.
It had to be done.
Are you listening?
Lily,
are you listening?
You see, you just needed
a bit of motivation.
There's a storage device on him.
A USB key, retrieve it.
(uneasy music)
(thugs speaking French)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(thug speaking French)
- Boss.
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(thug speaking French)
(soft music)
- [The Voice] Lily,
do you have the key, Lily?
- [Lily] Yes, I have it.
- [The Voice] Good job.
Now drop it off at the
location I'm sending you now.
- What's on it?
- [The Voice] Information tying
Marcel
to officials and members of
your agency who are corrupt.
Seems Marcel thought it was best
to hide it right under their
noses.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- [The Voice] Let's just say
justice will be served.
- After I do this,
you'll let John go?
- [The Voice] We'll
discuss your husband's fate
once you've completed the task.
- So my boss reached out with
the idea
of me starting to work remotely.
(soft music)
Get outta city.
Why aren't you excited?
(soft music continues)
Did you move my ladder?
- Why?
- To get on my level.
(soft music continues)
Hey, look at me, look at me.
You're good.
- Yeah.
(soft music continues)
♪ Is the world really the same ♪
♪ As I sit here instead ♪
♪ Is there meaning ♪
♪ Should I feel ♪
♪ How did this all go all so
wrong ♪
♪ Cause if it's all gone ♪
♪ To the even summation, so ♪
♪ This is the moment ♪
♪ That I see you stand ♪
♪ What was fine until ♪
♪ What we try to take down ♪
(phone ringing)
- [The Voice] You're
deviating from the path, Lily.
- I wanna talk to John.
- [The Voice] That's not
how this fucking works.
- That's how it's gonna work now
or I'm about to toss this
USB out the fucking window.
- [The Voice] Fine.
- [John] Lily.
Lily, is that you?
- John?
- [John] I'm so scared, baby.
I don't, I don't even know where
I am.
- I am so sorry, John.
- [John] What?
- For everything.
- [John] What are you saying?
- For making you feel isolated,
for--
- [John] Please, Lily.
- Work always coming first,
and--
- [John] What?
- [The Voice] All right.
Bring him here.
- For not being able to save
you.
- [The Voice] Come here, John.
- I can't save you, John.
- [The Voice] Time's up.
- But I need you to know that
I love you more than anything.
- [The Voice] Say goodnight,
John.
- John!
I love you, John.
(John screaming)
- [The Voice] What are you
planning, Lily?
We don't have time for this.
- You thought you had me
all figured out, didn't you?
Really did your research.
- [The Voice] Don't do this.
- You knew what kidnapping
John would do to me.
That I could bear see him go
through what I went through.
- [The Voice] Lily, we can work
this.
- You thought I'd fall in line
if I believe justice was being
served.
- [The Voice] Think about this,
Lily.
- Well, you're not some
vigilante.
My guess is you're one
of the names on this key.
- [The Voice] Okay, Lily, I'm
warning you.
- No, I'm warning you.
Once I'm done here,
I'm coming for you.
So you better find a good
hiding spot, motherfucker.
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- [Person On Phone] What
do we do if she interferes?
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(door creaking)
- Hello?
(uneasy music)
Lily.
(uneasy music continues)
Lily?
(tense music)
What the hell?
- I'm sorry.
I need to know I can trust you.
- Trust me?
- Hands up.
(tense music continues)
Sit down.
- You have a lot of explaining
to do.
(tense music continues)
- How long have we known each
other?
- I don't know, seven, eight
years.
- Nine.
- Okay, nine.
- In those nine years, have
you ever known me to lie?
- No.
- Deceive?
- Break the law?
- No.
Lily, it's me, Cindy, you can
talk to me.
- You know when I was kidnapped,
the uncertainty,
the fear,
it changed me,
changed us, John and I.
(tense music)
- I can imagine.
- You never really get
over something like that.
It does something to you.
Leaves a scar.
When I got out,
I was lost.
If it hadn't have been for John.
- Where are you going with this?
If you need help,
we can get that.
- Cindy,
you're not gonna like this.
(thug speaking French)
- This
sounds
almost unbelievable.
You're telling me that John's
dead,
that you,
you killed Guy?
- I was manipulated,
but I'm here now and
I wanna make it right.
- Manipulated by who?
- My current guess is someone in
power,
maybe within our own agency.
That's why I had to be careful.
- How sure are you?
- This sure.
- Okay.
I understand.
I'll be right in.
The sting is already underway.
- We have to warn them.
- Leave it to me.
You've done enough for tonight.
- No.
- Nikolai gave me the
location of Marcel's compound.
He's gonna slip away.
- This isn't something you
can handle on your own.
I'll take the intel to HQ.
I'll call you when I have an
update.
Lily.
(soft music)
(engines revving)
(uneasy music)
- Don't you get it?
Marcel wanted me here.
- There's two types of people
that could have done this.
One's on the streets
or the ones in power.
- Are the people in power
working for LaFleur?
- You don't want to know.
- Does this have something to do
with John?
- [The Voice] It was a diversion
for him and your people
to do the real exchange.
- [Cindy] The man who just
left here is Mr. White.
He owns a specialised unit.
He believes you should take a
lead.
- [Mr. White] You think
she has what it takes?
(gun shot fires)
- Mr. White?
(tense music)
(soft music)
(artist singing in foreign
language)
(uneasy music)
- One of your agents keeps
crossing paths with me.
One might take that as
an attempt on my life.
- What agent?
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- What?
- Don't play dumb.
(uneasy music continues)
- You're making a mistake.
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(quiet music)
(suspenseful music)
(fire exploding)
(suspenseful music continues)
(gun shots firing)
(thugs yelling)
(artist singing in foreign
language)
(gun shot fires)
(artist continues singing
in foreign language)
(Lily screams)
(gun shot fires)
(artist continues singing
in foreign language)
(knife slicing)
(artist continues singing
in foreign language)
(soft music)
(uneasy music)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(Lily speaking French)
(Lily screaming)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(uneasy music)
(knife slicing)
(LaFleur laughing)
- Shh.
(LaFleur speaking in French)
(Lily spitting)
(uneasy music continues)
(LaFleur laughing)
(soft music)
(tense music)
(punches thudding)
(both grunting)
(tense music continues)
(punches thudding)
(both grunting)
(tense music continues)
(LaFleur speaking in French)
- No.
I'm gonna kill you.
(tense music continues)
(punches thudding)
(both grunting)
(table breaking)
(LaFleur breathing heavily)
(Lily gasping)
(suspenseful music)
(chain bashing)
(suspenseful music continues)
(Lily grunting)
(soft music)
(LaFleur groaning)
(punches thudding)
(both grunting)
(soft music)
(punches thudding)
(both grunting)
(soft music continues)
(bones cracking)
(LaFleur screaming)
(soft music continues)
(triumphant music)
(soft music)
(gentle music)
Ma'am Why am I here?
I was supposed to be debriefing.
- You are,
but it's me who'll be
doing the debriefing.
Have a look.
- What is this?
- [Cindy] Aren't you
least bit curious, Lily?
- [Lily] I don't understand.
- You will if you have a seat.
As you can see, John is fine.
He was never in danger.
- How is this possible?
- AI was used to simulate his
voice.
- Why?
- Well, some would say
motivation,
but mostly to see if you can
function
in extreme circumstances.
- You mean a test?
- Exactly.
Not only did you pass,
you excelled.
- According to who?
- The division you applied to.
It operates in the shadows
using unconventional tactics
to gain valuable intelligence
and bring criminals to
justice as you've done.
- But I killed people.
I broke the law.
- Like I said, unconventional.
- [Lily] Mr. White.
- He works for me.
It's my unit, Lily.
(soft music)
- You put me through this?
You wanted Marcel dead?
- No.
I wanted his intel without
anyone knowing of its existence.
Marcel's death was
well, happy byproduct.
- A happy fucking byproduct?
- I apologise for the
theatricality of it all,
but it was necessary.
- You profiled me,
John, kidnapping.
You knew I'd bring the intel to
you.
- I made an educated guess
that you can complete the
mission.
Yes.
- You used me.
- What we do is hard
and requires sacrifice.
Remember,
you applied to the division.
- So what now?
- Now,
you have to make a choice.
(soft music)
You can join my team,
the real team.
I always knew you were capable.
Now you've proven it.
But I'll demand even more of
you.
Your marriage.
John can never know the truth,
or
you can return to your life.
(rock music)
♪ There goes my friend ♪
(rock music continues)
- [Cindy] But due to your
knowledge
of our organisation and
activity,
you'll no longer be able to at
the agency
and you'll be under surveillance
for the rest of life.
♪ There goes my friend ♪
♪ Til the end ♪
(rock music continues)
♪ There goes my friend ♪
♪ Til the end ♪
(rock music continues)
(artist screaming lyrics)
♪ Go tell it all ♪
♪ Tell another thing ♪
(artist singing indistinctly)
♪ Go tell it all ♪
♪ Tell another thing ♪
(artist singing indistinctly)
(rock music continues)
♪ There goes my friend ♪
(artist singing indistinctly)
(rock music)
♪ There goes my friend ♪
(rock music continues)
♪ Til the end ♪
(artist singing indistinctly)
(electronic music)